my name is michelle herbaspar
this is my manual life story
it was in september 2016 when i took
steps to get an insurance policy that
will secure myself as well as my
immediate family
yunkai
[Music]
and it is one of the best decisions i've
made in my life now october 14 2020 i
proposed sahanse glenn a boyfriend of 10
years at indiana delavan escape i said
yes
after myanmar proposed my fiancee and i
started planning our wedding we made
sure that we were prepared financially
because we invested in a manual life
plan early on i am proud to say that we
had a debt-free wedding celebration
[Music]
received
out from manulife three weeks before
nakasel namin
[Music]
blessing talaga
if you're making a huge life decision
like getting married the patneren clear
financial priorities
go on a budget plan and shampre stick
with it
bonus if my reliable partner got to
support you like manulife
[Music]
you